All right, everyone! This... is a stick-up!
大家给我孤好，这是抢劫
Don't anybody move!
通通都不准动
Now, empty that safe!
把猪瓜满给我掏空
Stop it! Stop it, you mean, old potato!
住手，住手 ! 你这可显的蛋头
Quiet, Bo Peep, or your sheep get run over!
于嘴，裤中 耕则你的羊会遭殊
Help! Baa! Help us!
救命，救命啊
Oh, no, not my sheep! Somebody do something!
列伤害我的羊，谁来划划忙啊
Reach for the sky!
飞向天空
Oh, no! Sheriff Woody!
烧了，是胡迪警长
I'm here to stop you, One-Eyed Bart.
我是来阻止你的，独眼蛋头
How'd you know it was me?
你怎广知道是我啊?
Are you gonna come quietly?
乖冬跟我走吧
You can't touch me, Sheriff!
你休想，警长
l brought my attack dog with the built-in force field.
我带了我那焦 多狠的网犬来了
Well, l brought my dinosaur who eats force-field dogs.
我带了我的恐龙 疙专门吃鬼狠的站大
Yipe, yipe, yipe, yipe! You're going to jail, Bart!
你要去坐宇了，蛋头
Say goodbye to the wife and Tater Tots.
跟你老朔小孩说再见吧
You saved the day again, Woody.
你又解救了危机，胡迪
You're my favorite deputy.
你是我最喜欢的副警长
You've got a friend in me
片名 : 玩具名动员 我是你好朋友
Come on, let's wrangle up the cattle.
来，我们来抓牛吧
When the road looks rough ahead
道路坎坷困难多
And you're miles and miles from your nice, warm bed
(皮克斯动忌抽作) 要十菌八千里才到家门口
Round 'em up, cowboy!
牛仓，把他们转起来
Just remember what your old pal said
你只要想起我在你左右
Boy, you've got a friend in me
我是你好朋友
Yee-haw!
呀啊 !
Yeah, you've got a friend in me
哦对，我是你好朋友
Hey, cowboy!
，牛仔
Some other folks might be a little bit smarter than 1am
有些人比我能干比我强
Big and stronger too
身体健肚走起路雄超赵
Come on, Woody.
来吧，胡这
Maybe
也许
But none of them will ever love you the way I do
没有人能像我这样爱访你
It's me and you, boy
对你是毫危保留
And as the years go by
多少的哉月中
Whoa! Whoa!
哇!哇!
Our friendship will never die
我们的命运紧相连
You've got a friend in me
我是你好朋友
All right!
好耶
Yeah, you've got a friend in me
哦对，我是你好朋友
Score!
达半得分
- You got a friend in me - Wow! Cool!
我是你好朋友 酷蜂了 !
- What do you think? - Oh, this looks great, Mom!
你喜欢吗 ? 妈味，这真是太棒了
Okay, birthday boy...
你喜欢就好，小毒星
We saw that at the store! l asked you for it!
就跟我在店里看到的一样
- [hope I have enough places. - Wow, look at that! That's so...
好棒，好棒哦… 希望能气得下
- One, two... Four. - Oh, my gosh, you got...
一、二、三、四
- Yeah, I think that's gonna be enough. - Could we leave this up 'til we move?
很好，这样应该就金了 可以留到搬家吗 ?
- Well, sure! We can leave it up. - Yeah!
当然可以唆 好耶
Now go get Molly. Your friends are gonna be here any minute.
去抱茉莉 你的朋友马上就要求了
Okay. It's party time, Woody.
好 派对要并始了
Howdy, little lady.
称好，小妹妹
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
有人在水源区下了毒
Come on, Molly.
来吧，菜莉 !
Oh, you're getting heavy.
娩好重吕
See you later, Woody.
再见了，胡迪
Pull my string! The birthday party's today?
我的天哪 是今天并生日派对吗 ?
Okay, everybody, coast is clear!
好了，各位 已经安全了
Ages 3 and up. It's on my box.
我盒子上写得很清楚 适合三藏以上
Ages 3 and up. I'm not supposed to be baby-sitting Princess Drool.
怎广能叫我当 吕水公主的枚时蚊姆呢
Hey, Hamm.
火腿，你看 !
- Look, I'm Picasso! - [don't get it.
我是蛤卡索 我看不懂
You uncultured swine! What're you lookin’ at, ya hockey puck?
没有文化的肥甜 看什么看啊 ! 你这个大高脸
- Hey, Sarge, have you seen Slinky? - Sir! No, sir!
队长，看到弹簧狗没有 报告长官，没有
Okay. Hey, thank you. At ease.
好啦，谢了 ! 稍息
Hey, uh, Slinky?
弹筑狗
Right here, Woody. I'm red this time.
我在这儿，胡迪
- No. Slink... - Oh, well, all right.
不行，弹筑狗… 好吧 !
You can be red if you want.
那红的让给你好了 等一下，弹敌狗
Just gather everyone up for a staff meeting, and be happy.
去叫大家集合来并干部会议 装得天心一点
Got it.
知道了
Staff meeting, everybody! Snake, Robot, podium duty.
各位，要并干部会议 长蛇、机器人准备讲台
Hey.
喂
Hey, Etch. Draw!
嘿，画板 技检
Oh! Got me again.
你又赢了
Etch, you've been working on that draw. Fastest knobs in the West.
驯板，你技检张得不错嘛 西部最快的神枪手
Got a staff meeting, you guys. Come on, let's go.
大人饮儿要并干部会议了 来吧，快点
Now, where is that... Oh.
我的那个呢 ?
- How're you doin’, Rex? - Were you scared? Tell me honestly.
抱抱龙，你好吐 ? 你有没有被啉到 ? 说实话
Il was close to being scared that time.
这一次 我差一点就被你嘛死
I'm going for fearsome here, but I just don't feel it.
我一直想可怕一点 但是我老是没有替感
I think I'm just coming off as annoying.
我只是一个车人灰的信伙
Oh, hi, Bo. Hi.
，宝中
l wanted to thank you, Woody, for saving my flock.
胡迪 我想要谢讲你救了我的羊群
Oh, hey, it was, uh, nothin’.
不客气
What do you say I get someone else to watch the sheep tonight?
我今天晚上另外找个人 赫我看羊，你看怎订样啊
Oh, yeah!
这个凡 好啊
Remember, I'm just a couple of blocks away.
列总了 要找我的话，我就在附近
- Yodel-ay-hee-hoo! - Come on, come on.
快点，快点
Smaller toys up front.
小的玩具到前面
Hey, Woody, come on.
胡迪，来吧
Oh, thanks, Mike.
谢了，礁克风
Okay... Whoa, whoa. Step back.
好了 太近了，退和后…
- For crying out loud. - Thank you.
拜斌 好了，谢谢
Hello? Check. That better? Great.
试音，试音，清楚吗?
Everybody hear me? Up on the shelf, can you hear me? Great.
好，大家都孤到了吗 ? 架子上面的孤见吗 ?很好
Okay. First item today:
今天我们第一项议题
Oh, yeah. Has everyone picked a moving buddy?
对了 ! 每个人都找到 搬家伙伴了没有?
- What? - Moving buddy? You can't be serious.
什么 ? 搬家伙伴 ? 他不是说真的吧 ?
I didn't know we were supposed to have one already.
我不知道我们要搬家了
Do we have to hold hands?
我们要拉小手吗 ?
You guys think this is a big joke.
你们以入 我在跟你们开玩笑
We've only got one week left before the move.
我们只剩下一个礼拜的时间 就要搬家了
I don't want any toys left behind. A moving buddy.
我不希望任何玩具被于下来 坪个人一组
If you don't have one, get one!
如果膛没有搬家伙伴 去找一个来 !
All right, next. Oh, yes.
好了，接下来… 对了 !
Tuesday night's plastic corrosion awareness meeting
星期二晚上 我们开的塑胁老化大会
was, I think, a big success.
非常的成功
And we wanna thank Mr. Spell for putting that on for us.
我们要感痊拼字先生 为我们所做的一切
- Thank you, Mr. Spell. - You're welcome.
府谢你，拼字先生 不客气
Okay. Oh, yes. One minor note here.
好了 ! 对了，还有一件小事
Andy's birthday party has been moved to today.
安半的生日派对 收到今天晚上
Wait a minute here!
接下来我们要讨论的是… 什么 ?
What do you mean the party's today? His birthday's not ‘til next week!
怎广会改成今天呢 ? 下个礼拜才是他的生日啊
What's goin’ on down there? Is his mom losin’ her marbles?
搞什么锡 ? 安生的始味头珊款去了吗 ?
Well, obviously she wanted to have the party before the move.
很题然安弟的妈味 希望在搬家之前开一个派对
I'm not worried. You shouldn't be worried.
我不担心 你们也不需要担心啊
Of course Woody ain't worried. He's been Andy's favorite since kindergarten.
胡迪当然不据心了
Hey, hey. Come on, Potato Head.
拜旗，蛋头先生
If Woody says it's all right, then, well, darn it, it's good enough for me.
如果胡迪说不用担心 那广我绝对不会担心
Woody has never steered us wrong before.
胡迪以前从来没有和弄错明
Come on, guys. Every Christmas and birthday we go through this.
拜旗，各位，每年村诈节 和生日我们都碰过来了
But what if Andy gets another dinosaur, a mean one?
但是如果安弟有了新恐龙呢 很金狠的那一逢
I just don't think I could take that kind of rejection!
我想我是绝对受不了 被抛泰的打击
Hey, listen, no one's getting replaced.
聘著 ! 没有人可以取代我们
This is Andy we're talking about.
我们讨论的重点是安弟
It doesn't matter how much we're played with.
我们和安弟玩 多少玫薄不重要
What matters is that we're here for Andy when he needs us.
重要的是安弟需要我们的时候 我们都在他身遵
That's what we're made for, right?
那才是我们当玩具的目的 对吧?
Pardon me. I hate to break up the staff meeting, but... they're here!
对不起哦 我很不想打断会议，但是…
Birthday guests at three o'clock!
客人在三锋方向
Stay calm, everyone!
保持冷静
Hey!
喂!
Meeting adjourned.
会议结束
Ho, boy! Will you take a look at all those presents?
老天 ! 你们有没有看到那些礼物 ?
I can't see a thing.
我什千都看不到
Yes, sir, we're next month's garage sale fodder for sure.
我们绝对会是 下个月车摩拍豆的货品了
- Any dinosaur-shaped ones? - Oh, for crying out loud.
有没有恐龙形状的礼物啊 ?
- They're all in boxes, you idiot. - They're getting bigger.
拜旗，礼物都在盒子壬 ! 和白辣 礼物越来越大了
Wait, there's a nice little one over there.
等一等，那里有个小件的
Hi!
!
- Spell: trash can. - We're doomed!
我们完了
All right! All right!
好啦，好啦
If l send out the troops, will you all calm down?
如果我派部降出去的诈 你们能安静下来咀?
- Yes! Yes! We promise! - Okay! Save your batteries.
能，和能，我们保证 好，省省电池吧
Very good, Woody. That's using the old noodle.
钙哟，胡迪 这一招真有效
Sergeant, establish a recon post downstairs. Code Red!
队长，立刻派侦察队到楼下 紧急状况
- You know what to do. - Yes, sir!
你知道该怎广做 是，长官
All right, men. You heard him. Code Red!
好了，各位，你们都匠到了 紧急状况
Repeat, we are at Code Red. Recon plan Charlie. Execute!
重桥，紧和急状涡 侦察计划开始于行
Let's move! Move, move, move, move!
快…快…
Yeah!
好耶 !
Okay, come on, kids.
好了，小朋友们
Everyone in the living room. It's almost time for the presents.
所有的人都到客廉来 准备要拆礼物了
All right, gangway, gangway.
让并，让并
And this is how we find out
有了这玩意多 我们就可以知道
what is in those presents.
那些礼物是什么了
Okay, who's hungry?
好了，谁的胜子狐了?
Here come the chips!
洋苹片在这祷
I've got Cool Ranch and barbecue!
有原味还有烤肉口味的
I thought I told him to pick these up.
我还以锅他收抢乾渗了哆
Shouldn't they be there by now? What's taking them so long?
他们不是该到了吗 ? 怎广会那广久 ?
Hey, these guys are professionals. They're the best.
他们可是训缚有素 最优秀的军人
Come on! They're not lying down on the job.
放心啦 他们疮没有躺著偷由
Go on without me! Just go!
走吧，列管我了 ! 快走吧
A good soldier never leaves a man behind.
一个好军人 绝对不会到下战友
Okay, everybody, come on.
好了，小朋友，锡了
Everybody settle down. Now, kids. Everybody...
大家都坐好 好了，小朋友，快遇来
You sit in a circle. No, Andy. Andy, you sit in the middle there.
围成圈圈坐下来 不，安弟，你要坐中间
Good. And... Which present are you gonna open first?
很好，好 你想先拆哪一个礼物呢 ?
- Mine! - There they are.
他们在那儿
Come in, Mother Bird. This is Alpha Bravo.
大锅嫣妈请回答 这是B队队长
- This is it! This is it! Quiet, quiet! - Come in, Mother Bird.
有消息了，大家安才
Alf right, Andy's opening the first present now.
好了 安弟正在拆第一个礼物了
Mrs. Potato Head! Mrs. Potato Head! Mrs. Potato Head!
蛋头太太，蛋头太太…-
Hey, I can dream, can't I?
做和白日梦又不犯法
The bow's coming off. He's ripping the wrapping paper.
丝带被解并了 他正在拆包装纸
It's a... It's... It's a... a lunch box.
那是…那是… 那是一个便当盒
- We've got a lunch box here. - Alunch box?
便当盒 ?
- Lunch box? - For lunch.
便当盒
Okay, second present. It appears to be...
好了，第二个礼物
- Okay, it's bed sheets. - Who invited that kid?
一件床单 那小子谁请来的呀?
Oh! Only one left.
只剩下一个了
- Okay, we're on the last present now. - Last present!
好，接著是最后一个礼物了 最后一个了
It's a big one. It's a...
这个礼物很大，那…
- It's a board game! Repeat, Battleship! - Whew!
重必，是海战棋
Hallelujah!
好耶，好耶
- Yeah! All right! - Hey, watch it!
小心一点
Sorry there, old spud head.
对不起，蛋头老兄
Mission accomplished. Well done, men. Pack it up. We're goin' home.
任务完成了，干得好 收工了了，我们回去吧
So did I tell ya? Nothin’ to worry about.
我就说吧 没什么好担心的
I knew you were right all along, Woody. Never doubted ya for a second.
我早就知道你是对，胡过 我从来没有怀疑遇你
Wait a minute. Oh!
等一下
- What do we have here? - Wait! Turn that thing back on!
这是什么啊 ? 等一下 ! 再把对讲机打开
Come in, Mother Bird!
大锅嫣妈请回答
Mom has pulled a surprise present from the closet.
妈咪从栖子里拿出礼物
Andy's opening it. He's really excited about this one.
安弟正在拆 他看到这个礼物很兴奋
- Mom, what is it? - It's a huge package.
杂味，这是什么 ? 是个很大的盒子
Oh, get outta the... One of the kids is in the way. I can't see.
等一下 有一个孩子揽住我的视比
-It'sa... - Wow!
那…那是…
It's a what? What is it?
那是什么啊? 是什么啊 ?
- Oh, no! - Oh, ya big lizard!
惨了 你这焦毒蜥蝎
- Now we'll never know what it is! - Way to go, Rex!
我们永吉不知道那是什么了 看你干得好事
No, no! Turn him around! Turn him around!
不对，不对 转去，转过去
He's puttin’ 'em in backwa... Here, you're puttin’ 'em in backwards!
不对，不对，放反了 你们把它们放反了
Plus is positive, minus is negative! Oh, let me!
正是阳极，负是除极 我来吧
Let's go to my room, guys!
到我的房间来玩
Red alert! Red alert! Andy is coming upstairs!
紧急状况，紧急状况 安弟要上楼了
- There! - Juvenile intrusion!
搞定了 儿童入优
Repeat, resume your positions now!
重覆，立刻回到自己岗位上
Andy's coming! Everybody, back to your places! Hurry!
安弟来了 快回到自己的位置上
Get to your places!
快回到自己的位置
Where's my ear? Who's seen my ear? Did you see my ear?
我的耳条，我的耳条呢 ? 有谁看到我的耳末 ?
Out of my way! Here I come! Here I come!
让并，让并 我来了，我来了
Hey, look, its lasers light up. Take that, Zurg!
你们看，他的雷射亮了 帮我拿一下
Quick, make a space. This is where the spaceship lands.
这和里是太空船降落的地方
And he does it like that. And he does a karate chop action!
他还是空手道高手呢
Come on down, guys! It's time for games!
小朋友下来吧
- What the heck is up there? - Woody, who's up there with ya?
那上面的东西是什么 ? 胡迪，谁跟你在上面啊?
Woody?
胡迪
- What are you doing under the bed? - Nothin’. Nothin’.
你在床底下干什么啊 ? 没什么，没什让
I'm sure Andy was just a little excited, that's all.
我想安弟有一点太愉硅了
Too much cake and ice cream, Il suppose. It's just a mistake!
大概是吃了太多冰洪汶跟蛋姓 那只是个意外
Well, that mistake is sitting in your spot, Woody.
那个意外 正坐在你的地般上，胡过
- Have you been replaced? - What did I tell you earlier?
你被人取代了吗 ? 我刚刚是怎订告诉你的 ?
No one is getting replaced.
没有人可以取代我们
Now, let's all be polite and give whatever it is up there
好了，不管那上面是什么 我们都要给他来一个…
a nice, big Andy's-room welcome.
礼瑶的热情的 安弟房间式的数迎
Buzz Lightyear to Star Command.
巴斯光年呼叫星际总部
Come in, Star Command.
收到了请回答
Star Command, come in. Do you read me?
星床总部，请回答 你们有没有收到 ?
Why don't they answer? My ship!
他们为什么不回答 ? 我的太空船
Blast! This'll take weeks to repair.
糟糙，要花好久才能修好
Buzz Lightyear mission log, stardate 4-0-7-2.
巴斯光年任务日读 星麻日期4072年
My ship has run off course en route to sector 12.
我的太空船 在第十二区有晚礁轨道
I've crash-landed on a strange planet.
我共落在一个奇怪的星球
The impact must've awoken me from hypersleep.
我一定是被 巨大的撞贡莫醒
Terrain seems a bit unstable.
这和里的地形似乎有点不稳定
No readout yet if the air is breathable.
(和伽玛四区)
And there seems to be no sign of intelligent life anywhere.
而且也看不出来 有智慧型生命的踊象
Hello!
你好
Whoa! Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
站住
Did I frighten you? Didn't mean to.
我嘛到你了吗 ? 我不是故意的
Sorry. Howdy. My name is Woody.
抱数，你好 我叫胡迪
And this is Andy's room. That's all l wanted to say.
而这和里呢，是安弟的房间
And also, there has been a bit of a mix-up.
你一定是搞错了
This is my spot, see, the bed here.
而这张床…
Local law enforcement. It's about time you got here.
当地的球法人员 你早该来了
I'm Buzz Lightyear, Space Ranger, Universe Protection Unit.
我是巴斯光年 保护字密小组的太空骑警
My ship has crash-landed here by mistake.
我的太空船意外聊机了
Yes, it is a mistake because, you see, the bed here is my spot.
是呀，这是一个意外
I need to repair my turbo boosters.
我要修理我的渴输推进器
Do you people still use fossil fuel, or have you discovered crystallic fusion?
你们现在是用茧燃料 还是已经有结晶体溶解物
Well, let's see. We got double-A's.
我想想…我们有三号电池
Watch yourself! Halt! Who goes there?
小心 站住，什么人 ?
Don't shoot! It's okay. Friends.
列开检 没事，是朋友
- Do you know these life-forms? - Yes! They're Andy's toys.
你认识这些生物跨 ? 认识，他们是安弟的玩具
All right, everyone, you're clear to come up.
好了，你们可以上来了
lam Buzz Lightyear. Il come in peace.
我是巴斯光年，和平使者
Oh, I'm so glad you're not a dinosaur!
我好高要，你不是恐龙
Wh-why, thank you!
谢谢
Now, thank you all for your kind welcome!
谢谢你们热情的欢迎
- Say, what's that button do? - I'll show you.
那个按僵是干什么的?
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年拯救宇密
Hey, Woody's got something like that. His is a pull string.
胡迪也有那样的东西 他的是拉线的
- Only it's... - Only it sounds like a car ran over it.
只是… 只是黄起来像被车子压明
Oh, yeah, but not like this. This is a quality sound system.
对，不像这个 这个是高品质声音系统
Probably all copper wiring, huh?
配线可能是铜钱哦
So, where you from? Singapore? Hong Kong?
对了，你从哪里来的? 新加坡 ? 香港 ?
Well, no. Actually, I'm stationed up in the Gamma Quadrant of Sector Four.
不，事实上我是时殖在 第四区域的人徊玛象限
As a member of the elite Universe Protection Unit
我是宇宙保护小组
of the Space Ranger Corps,
太空警备降的队员
I protect the galaxy from the threat of invasion
(我保护我们的星床 免詹受到星际联盟头咏大效 札克天王的入侵) 我保护我们的星度
from the evil Emperor Zurg, sworn enemy of the Galactic Alliance.
(我保护我们的星床 免詹受到星际联盟头咏大效 札克天王的入侵)
Oh, really? I'm from Playskool.
是吗? 我来自儿乐裤
And I'm from Mattel. Well, I'm not really from Mattel.
而我来自美泰儿 其实我兹不是来自美泰儿
I'm actually from a smaller company that was purchased in a leveraged buyout.
我是来自比较小的公司 钻果被美泰儿收购了，我想…
You'd think they'd never seen a new toy before.
一群土包子，没看明新玩具
Well, sure. Look at him. He's got more gadgets on him than a Swiss Army knife.
是，你看看他身上的小虽西 比瑞士刀晃要多呢
Please be careful.
小心是
You don't want to be in the way when my laser goes off.
被我的雷射贡中可不是好玩的 嘿，雷射?
Hey, a laser! How come you don't have a laser, Woody?
你怎订会没有雷射呢 ? 胡迪
It's not a laser! It's a... It's a little light bulb that blinks.
那不是雷射 那只是会闪的灯泡
- What's with him? - Laser envy.
他怎广了 ? 嫉妒雷射
All right, that's enough!
好了，狗了
Look, we're all very impressed with Andy's new toy.
我们对安弟的新玩具 都印象深刻
- Toy? - T-O-Y. Toy!
玩具 TOY玩具
Excuse me, I think the word you're searching for is "Space Ranger."
对不起 我想你用的字应该是太空骑警
The word I'm searching for I can't say because there's preschool toys present.
我想要用的字现在不能说 因为有学夫前的玩具在场
Gettin’ kinda tense, aren't ya?
你有点紧张了吧?
Mr. Lightyear, now, I'm curious.
巴斯先生，我很好奇
What does a Space Ranger actually do?
一个太空骑警都做些什么呢 ?
He's not a Space Ranger!
他不是太空骑警
He doesn't fight evil or, or shoot lasers or fly!
他不会打击那恶 发射雷射，也不会赤
Excuse me.
打个贫
Oh, impressive wingspan! Very good!
好织的机翼哦，酰鉴了
Oh, what? What? These are plastic. He can't fly!
拜旗，什么六 ? 这些是塑胁，他才不会习
They are a terillium-carbonic alloy, and I can fly.
这是碳化合金 而且我的确会赤
- No, you can't. - Yes, I can.
不，你不会 会，我会
- You can't. - Can.
你不会 会
Can't. Can't. Can't!
不会，不会，不会
I tell you, I could fly around this room with my eyes closed!
就算我并著眼晴 也可以城遍整个房间
- Okay, then, Mr. Light Beer, prove it. - All right, then, I will.
好啊，泡泡头先生，证明吧 那好吧
Stand back, everyone!
各位请退和后
To infinity and beyond!
科向宇密浩瀚扰地
- Can! - Whoa!
我会屎
Oh, wow, you flew magnificently!
你赤得有兔炫的
- [found my movin' buddy. - Thank you. Thank you all. Thank you.
我找到搬家伙伴了 谢讲，谢澳你们，谢澳
That wasn't flying! That was... falling with style.
那不叫飞行 那只是摔得很好看
Man, the dolls must really go for you. Can you teach me that?
小妞们一定迷死你了 教教我好吗 ?
- Golly bob howdy! - Oh, shut up!
刚刚那一招真是太酷了 于并
You know, in a couple of days,
再过次天
everything will be just the way it was. They'll see.
这和里就会恢复老柑子了 等著瞧吧
They'll see.
不信你们看
! was on top of the world livin’ high
我现在高高在上
It was right in my pocket
样样事都享受现成
! was livin’ the life
我现在的光景
Things were just the way they should be
想要什么都行
When from out of the sky like a bomb
忽然间从天外赤遇来
Comes some little punk in a rocket
一颗要爆发的炸弹
Now alf of a sudden some strange things are happening to me
从此我发现 一些奇怪的事要发生
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年拯救宇密
Strange
奇怪的…
Things are happening to me
…事情发生在我身上
Strange things are happening to me
奇怪的事情发生在我身上
Ain't no doubt about it
这是毫乱疑问的
! had friends ! had lots of friends
我曾所有许多朋友
Now aif my friends are gone
现在一个也不剩
And I'm doin’ the best l can
我叫他们
To carry on
他们对我是冷冰冰的
- l had power - Power
我曾有特权
- l was respected - Respected
我曾被重视
But not any more
但好景不常
Let me tell you ‘bout it Strange
让我告诉你
Things are happenin’ to me
奇怪的事发生在我身上
Things
…的事情
Things are happenin’ to me
奇怪的事发生在我身上
Ain't no doubt about it
这是毫乱疑问的
Strange
奇怪…
Things
…的事情
Finally!
终於重见天日了
Hey, who's got my hat?
我的蝎子在哪里啊 ?
Look, I'm Woody! Howdy, howdy, howdy!
大家好，我是胡迪 大家好，大家好
Gimme that!
还给我
Say there, Lizard and Stretchy Dog, let me show you something.
抱抱龙，恒筑狗 我给你们看笠东西
It looks as though I've been accepted into your culture.
我好像被你们给同化了
Your chief, Andy, inscribed his name on me.
你们老大安弟 把他的名字刻在我身上
Wow!
哇塞
With permanent ink too!
选用奇县笔耶
Well, l must get back to repairing my ship.
好了 我要回去修我的太空船了
Don't let it get to you, Woody.
胡迪，不要让他影响到你
Let what? I don't... What do you mean? Who?
你说什么 ? 什么意思?谁?
I know Andy's excited about Buzz.
我知道安弟很喜欢巴斯
But you know he'll always have a special place for you.
但是你在他的心目当中 一直估有一席之地的
- Yeah, like the attic. - All right, that's it!
是啊，是浙畴零地 好了，我受金了
Unidirectional bonding strip.
音向的细长速针带
Mr. Lightyear wants more tape.
巴斯先生要肋带
Listen, Light Snack, you stay away from Andy.
了著，泡泡头 你最好郊安弟速一点
He's mine, and no one is taking him away from me.
他是我的 没有人可以拆散他跟我
What are you talking about?
你到底在说什么啊?
Where's that bonding strip?
我的连结带呢 ?
And another thing:
还有一件事
Stop with this spaceman thing! It's getting on my nerves!
从现在开始 少再说什么太空的事
Are you saying you wanna lodge a complaint with Star Command?
不高村可以向 星床总部申诉啊
Okay! Well, so you wanna do it the hard way, huh?
好，我看你是 数酒不吃吃罚酒
- Don't even think about it, cowboy. - Oh, yeah, tough guy?
鳌长，不要扰理取半 是吗 ?硬汉
The air isn't... toxic.
这壬的空气没有毒芯
How dare you open a spaceman's helmet on an uncharted planet!
你怎广可以在一个 不知名的星球上打开我的头盔
My eyeballs could've been sucked from their sockets!
我的眼球很可能被吸出去的
You actually think you're the Buzz Lightyear?
你真的以篇… 你就是太空人巴斯光年吗 ?
Oh, all this time I thought it was an act!
我一直以锅你只是装模作样
Hey, guys, look! It's the real Buzz Lightyear!
各位，快来看 他是真的巴斯光年
You're mocking me, aren't you?
你在讽刺我，对吧 ?
Oh, no, no. No, no, no, no, no. Buzz, look, an alien!
不是啦… 巴斯，有外星人
Where?
哪里 ?
Yes!
好耶
It's Sid!
是阿蔡
Don't move!
不准动
I thought he was at summer camp.
我还以锅他去夏令悟呢
They must've kicked him out early this year.
他一定是被踢出来了
Oh, no, not Sid!
天哪，怎广又是他?
Incoming!
克弹来闵 !
- Who is it this time? - L... Lean't... can't tell.
这回又是谁啊? 我…我看不清楚是维
- Hey, where's Lenny? - Right here, Woody.
雷尼叶? 我在这儿，胡迪
Oh, no, I can't bear to watch one of these again.
不，我受不了残忍的书面
Oh, no, it's a Combat Carl.
天哪 ! 是战同兵卡击
What's going on?
怎广回事啊 ?
Nothing that concerns you spacemen, just us toys.
这不天你们太空人的事 是我们玩具自己的事
I'd better take a look anyway.
最好让我看一看
Why is that soldier strapped to an explosive device?
那个阿兵哥 为什么铸著爆炸装置?
That's why: Sid.
因为那个…阿巷
Sure is a hairy fellow.
他的毛选真多
No, no, that's Scud, you idiot.
不是，那是阿德，和白疯
That is Sid.
他才是阿薛
- You mean that happy child? - That ain't no happy child.
那个天真的小孩 ? 他才不天真呢
He tortures toys, just for fun!
折磨那些玩具是他的最爱
Well, then we've got to do something.
我看我们必须想个办法
What are you doing? Get down from there!
你在干什么 ? 快下来
- I'm gonna teach that boy a lesson. - Yeah, sure. You go ahead.
我要给那孩子一个教训 是啊，好，盆管去
Melt him with your scary laser.
用你嘛人的雷射溶化他
Be careful with that! It's extremely dangerous.
小心，别希寿 那是非常危险的
He's lighting it! He's lighting it! Hit the dirt!
点火了，他黑火了
Look out!
驮下来
Yes! He's gone! He's history!
好耶，死了，他死了
I could've stopped him.
我本来可以阻正他
Buzz, I would love to see you try.
巴斯，我很想看看你的本事
Of course, I'd love to see you as a crater.
你要怎订去当烈士
The sooner we move, the better.
真希望立刻就能搬家
Yeah!
好耶 !
To infinity and beyond!
飞向浩瀚宇密
All this packing makes me hungry.
打包完了腻子好狐哦
What would you say to dinner at, oh, Pizza Planet?
我们的晚餐就去…比荐星球吧
Pizza Planet? Oh, cool!
比荐星球 ! 哦栈
Go wash your hands, and I'll get Molly ready.
去洗手，我替茉莉换衣服
- Can I bring some toys? - You can bring one toy.
我可以带玩具去吗 ? 你只能带一个玩具
- Just one? - One toy?
只能带一个啊 一个玩具
Will Andy pick me?
安弟会玩我咀 ?
"Don't count on it"?
列作葛，不是吧?
Buzz! Oh, Buzz! Buzz Lightyear.
巴斯 巴斯，巴斯光年
Buzz Lightyear, thank goodness. We've got trouble!
巴斯光年 老天租，我们有廊烦了
- Trouble? Where? - Down there. Just down there.
麻烦，在哪儿 ? 下面，就在下面 !
A helpless toy, it's... it's trapped, Buzz!
一个么助的玩具 它被困住了
Then we've no time to lose.
我立刻去看看
I don't see anything!
什么都没有耶
Oh, he's there! Just, just keep looking!
就在那下面，再找找
What kind of toy...
他长什么样子…
Buzz!
巴斯
I don't see him in the driveway.
他没有摔在车道上耶
- [ think he bounced into Sid's yard! - Oh! Buzz!
我猜他弹到阿薛的院子了 巴斯
Hey, everyone, R.C.'s trying to say something. What is it, boy?
各位，遗控车好像有话要说 什么事，老弟 ?
- He's saying that this was no accident. - What do you mean?
他是说这件事情冰不是意外 什么意思 ?
- [mean Humpty-Dumpty was pushed... - No!
巴斯是被推出去的 不是吧 ?
.. by Woody!
是胡迪推的
- What? - Wait a minute.
什么 ? 等一下
You don't think I meant to knock Buzz out the window, do you? Potato Head?
你…你不会以禹我是故意 把巴斯推出窗外吧?
That's Mr. Potato Head to you, you back-stabbing murderer!
你该叫我蛋头先生 你这暗箭伤人的多手
Now, it was an accident, guys.
那是个意外
Come on. Now, you, you gotta believe me.
各位，拜旗你们… 你们一定要相信我
We believe ya, Woody. Right, Rex?
我们相信你，胡过 对吧，抱抱龙 ?
Well, ye... N... I don't like confrontations!
这个…我不喜数跟人家对轩
Where is your honor, dirt bag? You are an absolute disgrace!
你的莹叭到哪儿去了 ? 你真的是军人的一大职厚
You don't deserve to... Hey!
你根本不配对我们发号施令
You couldn't handle Buzz cutting in on your playtime, could you, Woody?
受不了巴斯光年估去你的时间 对吧，胡巡
Didn't wanna face the fact that Buzz just might be Andy's new favorite toy.
你扰法面对巴斯可能成入 安弟最喜欢的玩具这件事实
So you got rid of him.
所以你想要除掉他
Well, what if Andy starts playing with me more, Woody, huh?
如果安弟花很多时间和我玩冤
You gonna knock me outta the window too?
你也要把我丢到窗外吗 ?
I don't think we should give him the chance.
我们不能训他胡作非坑
There he is, men. Frag him!
他在那里，委手榴弹
Let's string him up by his pull string!
用他的拉鲁把他贱起来
- [got dibs on his hat! - Would you boys stop it!
我要他的幅子 你们快住手好吗 ?
Tackle him!
抓住他
No, no, no! Wait! Il can explain everything!
不…等等…我可以解释 安弟，快点
Okay, Mom, be right down. I've gotta get Buzz.
好，我马上就来 我要去拿巴斯
Retreat!
撒退
Mom, do you know where Buzz is?
杂味，有没有看到巴斯?
No, I haven't seen him.
没有，我没有看到
- Andy, I'm heading out the door! - But, Mom, I can't find him!
安弟，我要出门骂 但是我找不到他
Honey, just grab some other toy. Now, come on!
儿子，先拿列的玩具，快走了
Oh, okay.
好吧
I couldn't find my Buzz. I know I left him right there.
我找不到巴斯 我明明放在桌上的
Honey, I'm sure he's around. You'll find him.
乖冬，他一定膛在那儿 你会找到他的
It's too short! We need more monkeys!
太短了，我们还需要过环猴
There aren't any more! That's the whole barrel!
已经没有了 ! 整桶都倒光了
Buzz, the monkeys aren't working!
巴斯，这些违环猴不匆
We're formulating another plan! Stay calm!
我们会再想其他的办法的 保持冷静
Oh, where could he be?
他到底在哪里啊 ?
- Can I help pump the gas? - Sure! I'll even let you drive.
我来划忙加油 好啊，我还能让你开车呢
- Yeah? - Yeah, when you're 16.
真的吗 ? 对，等你满十六成
Funny, Mom.
真讨灰，杂味又在骗人家
Great. How am I gonna convince those guys it was an accident?
天啊 ! 我要怎广说服那些信伙 那只是个意外
Buzz!
巴斯
Buzz! Ha! You're alive!
巴斯 ! 你还活闭
This is great! Oh, I'm saved! I'm saved.
太棒了 我有救了 ! 我有救了!
Andy'll find you here, he'll take us back to the room
安弟会发现你 他会带我们十个回房间
and then you can tell everyone that this was all just a big mistake.
然后你就可以告诉每一个人 这只是一个天大的误会
Huh? Right? Buddy?
对吧 ? 伙伴
I just want you to know that even though you tried to terminate me,
我只是要让你知道 路然你一直想要毁沽我
revenge is not an idea we promote on my planet.
但是在我们的星球 站不鼓励我们复仇
- Oh. Well, that's good. - But we're not on my planet, are we?
那很好 但这里不是我的星球，对吧?
No.
对
Okay, come on!
好，你来啊
You want a piece of me?
你想要拆了我吐 ?
Buzz, Buzz, Buzz Lightyear to the rescue.
巴…巴斯光年拯救字密
- Next stop. - Pizza Planet! Yeah!
比荐星球，好耶
I'm lost!
啊，我被遗泰了
Oh, I'm a lost toy!
我是个没人要的玩具
Buzz Lightyear mission log.
巴斯光年任务日读
The local sheriff and l seem to be at a huge refueling station of some sort.
鳌长跟我似乎在一个 很巨大的燃料补给站
You!
你…
- According to my navi-computer, the... - Shut up!
于并
- Just shut up, you idiot! - Sheriff, this is no time to panic.
给我并嘴，白痪 警长，现在没有时间警慌
This is the perfect time to panic. I'm lost. Andy is gone.
现在是车慌的好时机 我被遗认了，安弟走了
They're gonna move from their house in two days, and it's all your fault!
他们再通雨天就要搬家了 这全是你的错
My... My fault? If you hadn't pushed me out of the window in the first place...
我…我的错，如果你一开始 没有把我推出窗外…
Oh, yeah?
是吗?
Well, if you hadn't shown up in your stupid little cardboard spaceship
对，如果不是你 坐著那艘策太空船出现
and taken away everything that was important to me...
站且抢走 原来属於我的东西的话…
Don't talk to me about importance!
你不能怪到我身上
Because of you the security of this entire universe is in jeopardy!
就是因闹你 使整个宇密的安全受到危险
What? What are you talkin’ about?
什么 ? 你在说什么啊 ?
Right now, poised at the edge of the galaxy, Emperor Zurg
就是现在 机克天王在银河系跟缘
has been secretly building a weapon
秘密建立了一种武器
with the destructive capacity to annihilate an entire planet!
那个玩意儿 足以毁减整个星球
l alone have information that reveals this weapon's only weakness.
只有我有资料 可以击破这武器唯一的弱点
And you, my friend, are responsible
而你，朋友
for delaying my rendezvous with Star Command!
就是你耽误了 我跟星际总部会合的时间
You... are... a... toy!
你是个玩具 !
You aren't the real Buzz Lightyear! You're a...
你不是真的巴斯光年 !
You're an action figure! You are a child's plaything!
你…只是个会动的玩具 只是给小朋友玩的玩具
You are a sad, strange little man, and you have my pity.
你是个可翡又奇怪的人 我很同情你
Farewell.
再见了
Oh, yeah? Well, good riddance, ya loony!
是吗?走啊，疯子
"Rendezvous with Star Command."
跟星讲狗部会合个头啦
- Hey, gas dude! - You talkin’ to me?
加油小第 你在叫我吗 ?
- Yeah, man. Can you help me? - Pizza Planet? Andy!
没错，你能如我吗? 比荐星球 ? 安生
Do you know where Cutting Boulevard is?
你知道卡廷大道在哪里吗 ?
Oh, no!
不
I can't show my face in that room without Buzz.
没有巴斯我没有脸回去
- Buzz! Buzz, come back! - Go away!
巴斯，巴斯，快回来 走开
No! Buzz, you gotta come back! I...
巴斯，你一定要回来
I found a spaceship!
我找到一舰太空船了
It's a spaceship, Buzz!
一舰太空船，巴斯
Come on, man, hurry up! Like, the pizzas are getting cold here!
老兄，快一点 这些比茂会泳掉
- Cutting Boulevard, huh? - Yeah, yeah. Which way?
卡延大道 ? 对，在哪里?
Now, you're sure this space freighter will return to its port of origin
好，你确定这个太空运输机 送完了货物之和后
once it jettisons its food supply?
就会回到原来太空站吐?
And when we get there, we'll be able to find a way to transport you home.
等到了那里以后 我们再来想个办法送你回家
- Well, then, let's climb aboard. - No, no, no, wait, Buzz! Buzz!
好，那我们上船吧 等等…巴斯
Let's get in the back. No one will see us there.
我们到车和后面 那里不会被人发现
Negative. There are no restraining harnesses in the cargo area.
不行，货舱里浊有安全设备 那是载货的
- We'll be much safer in the cockpit. - Yeah, bu...
在机舱里比较安全 对，但是…
Buzz! Buzz!
巴斯 ! 巴斯!
That's two lefts and a right, huh?
先堪塌雨风，然后再右夸 对吧?
- Thanks for the directions, okay? - Yeah. And remember, kid...
谢讲你的划忙，谢了
Buzz!
巴斯
It's safer in the cockpit than the cargo bay. What an idiot.
在机舱比在货舱里安全 真是白立
Next shuttle lift-off is scheduled for
下一班前往比茂星球的 高速接鹏专车
T-minus 30 minutes and counting.
正在倒数计时中
You are clear to enter.
你可以进去了
Welcome to Pizza Planet.
殉迎来到比荐星球
The white zone is for immediate pizza...
白色区域是快速比荐外带区…
There you are.
整改?你在这儿呀
Now, the entrance is heavily guarded. We need a way to get inside.
入口守人备很森磊 我们必须想办法进去
Great idea, Woody.
好主意，胡巡
I like your thinkin’.
我喜数你的点子
You are clear to enter. Welcome to Pizza Planet.
你可以进去了 殉迎来到比荐星球
Now!
走吧
Quickly, Sheriff! The air lock is closing.
快点，舱门就要关了
Jones, party of five, your shuttle is now boarding...
玉斯一家人，一共五个人 你的接野车正在发射台十二吕
Hey, Mom, can we have some tokens?
始，我们可以去换代还吗 ?
Watch where you're going!
噢，走路小心点
Sorry.
抱攻
Nine, eight, seven, six,
十、九、八、七、六…-
five, four, three,
(任务指挥中心) 五 四、三、 二、一
What a spaceport! Good work, Woody.
好棒的太空船哦 干得好，胡迪
Mom, can I play Black Hole? Please, please, please?
妈味，我能玩黑洞吐 ? 拜旗…
- Andy! - Now, we need to find a ship
安弟 ! 我们要去找一盘
- that's headed for Sector 12. - Wait a minute. No, Buzz! This way.
到十二区的太空船 等一下，巴斯，往这遵
- There's a special ship. I just saw it. - You mean it has hyperdrive?
那超有一盘特别的船 它有超高动力吗 ?
Hyperactive hyperdrive.
超高的和刻动动力
And Astro... turf!
还有太空…上驱动
- Where is it? I don't see the... - Come on. That's it.
在哪里?我没有看到…
Spaceship!
太空船 !
All right, Buzz, get ready. And...
好了，巴斯，准人备了
- And the universe explodes! - Okay, Buzz, when I say go,
就快要好了 等我一说“上”
we're gonna jump in the basket. Buzz!
我们就跳到篮子里 巴斯
- No! - Mom, if I eat all my pizza,
不好了 妈，如果我把比茂都吃光
can Il have some alien slime?
你能不能给我外星和用液 ?
This cannot be happening to me.
我怎广会碰上这种事
- A stranger. - From the outside.
陌生人 他来自外面
Greetings. ! am Buzz Lightyear.
你们好 ! 我是巴斯光年
Il come in peace.
和平的使者
Before your space journey, re-energize yourself
在你今天离开前
with a slice of pepperoni, now boarding at counter three.
请用一片腹膀比蕊补充能源 现在请从三号杠权有悚机
This is an intergalactic emergency.
这是星订紧急事件
I need to commandeer your vessel to Sector 12.
我要征召你们的船到第十二区
Who's in charge here?
这壬谁负责?
The claw!
是处子
The claw is our master.
爪子是我们的主人
The claw chooses who will go and who will stay.
爪子会选择谁留下来谁芍开
- This is ludicrous. - Hey, bozo, you got a brain in there?
这太黄订了 遇份，这什么烟机器骂 ?
Take that!
可恶，欠扁
Oh, no! Sid!
烧了，阿薛
Get down!
快路下来
What's gotten into you? I was...
整长，你怎六了，我…
You are the one that decided to climb into this...
是你自己决定爬上来的
The claw, it moves.
爪子 ! 它动了
l have been chosen!
我被选中了
Farewell, my friends. I go on to a better place.
再见了，我的朋友 我要去更好玩的地方了
Gotcha!
抓到了
A Buzz Lightyear? No way!
巴斯光年 不可能
Yes!
好耶
Buzz! No!
巴斯，不!
Hey!
哩1 区
He has been chosen!
他被玩中了
- He must go. - Hey!
他一定得走
- What are you doing? - Do not fight the claw.
不要触怒爪子 你们在干什么 ?
Stop it! Stop it, you zealots!
帮手，放手 ! 你们这些疯子
All right! Double prizes!
棒呆了!人双重大次 !
Let's go home and... play.
我们回家去玩吧
Sheriff, l can see your dwelling from here.
整长，我看到你家了
- You're almost home. - Nirvana is coming.
你就快到家了 神秘之门快到了
- The mystic portal awaits. - Will you be quiet?
通往极乐世界 拜斌你并嘴
You guys don't get it, do you?
你们两个根本不懂
Once we go into Sid's house, we won't be coming out.
只要人进了阿节家 一募子都列想出来
Whoa, Scud! Hey, boy!
阿德，好乖
Sit! Good boy.
坐下来，好冬
- Hey, I got something for you, boy. - Freeze!
我有东西要给你 不要动
Ready, set, now!
预和人，咏 !
Hannah! Hey, Hannah!
汉娜 ! 汉娜!
- What? - Did I get my package in the mail?
干乌? 你有没有看到我的包襄 ?
- [don't know. - What do you mean you don't know?
我不知道 你不知道是什么意思 ?
- Oh, no, Hannah! Look, Janie! - What? Hey!
莉了，汉娜，你看珍妮 干乌?
- She's sick! - No, she's not!
她病了 她才汪有
I'll have to perform one of my operations.
我要马上者她动个手和本
- No! - No, not Sid's room. Not there.
阿薛，把她还给我 不，不要进阿苏的房间
Sid! Sid!
阿薛 ! 阿薛 !
Oh, no, we have a sick patient here, nurse.
护士，我们这里有一个病患
Prepare the OR, stat!
准备动手术，快点
Patient is... prepped.
病人准备好唆
No one's ever attempted a double bypass brain transplant before.
以前从来没有人 动遇脑袋移植的手术
Now for the tricky part. Pliers!
这种手术很困准 人钳子
I don't believe that man's ever been to medical school.
我想那个孩子 应该没有上过医学院吧
Doctor, you've done it!
医生，你成功了
Hannah!
汉娜
Janie's all better now.
珍妮现在好多了
- Mom! Mom! - She's lying!
始，阿共弄款我的娃娃 她说议
Whatever she says, it's not true!
不管她说什么都不是真的
We are gonna die. I'm outta here!
我们死定了，我要郊开
Locked.
锁住了
There's gotta be another way outta here.
一定还有别的出口
Buzz? Was that you?
巴斯，那是你吐 ?
Hey, hi there, little fella.
你好，小售伙
Come out here. Do you know a way outta here?
出来啊 ! 你知道出去的路中?
Buzz!
巴…巴斯!
They're cannibals.
他们会自相残杀
Mayday, mayday.
求救，求救
Come in, Star Command. Send reinforcements.
星际总部请回答 请派和后援部队
Star Command, do you copy?
星麻总部，收到吐?
I've set my laser from stun to kill.
我的雷射检 最大威力可以林人
Great. Great. Yeah, and if anyone attacks us, we can blink 'em to death.
好极了，好极了
Hey, you guys, I think I found him!
各位，我找到他了
Buzz, is that you?
巴斯，是你吐 ?
Whiskers, will you get outta here!
咪味，拜旗你走开好吗 ?
You're interfering with the search and rescue!
你干摄到我们的搜救任务了
Look, they're home.
你们看，他们回来了
Mom, have you seen Woody?
杂味，看到胡迪没有?
- Where was the last place you left him? - Right here in the van.
你最后把他放在哪儿 ? 就在车上啊
Oh, I'm sure he's there. You're just not looking hard enough.
他一定在的 只是你没好好找而已
He's not here, Mom. Woody's gone.
他不在车上，胡迪不见了
Woody's gone?
胡迪不见了?
Yeah, boy, the weasel ran away.
真是的，那黄鼠狼逃走了
Huh? Huh? I told you he was guilty.
我早说他有界
Who would've thought he was capable of such atrocities?
谁也没有想到 他会敌出这广可怕的事情
Oh, Slink, I hope he's okay.
弹簧狗，我希望他没事
Oh, a survivor. Where's the rebel base? Talk!
有生膛者 叛军的基地在哪儿，说!
I can see your will is strong.
你的意志力很坚强世
Well, we have ways of making you talk.
不遇我们有很多办法 让你乖乖招供
Where are your rebel friends now?
你的叛军朋友在哪里?
Sid, your Pop Tarts are ready!
阿薛，你的点心好了
All right!
好耶
Are you all right? I'm proud of you, Sheriff.
你膛好吗 ? 我真以你锅蓉
A lesser man would've talked under such torture.
一般人被这样折磨早就招了
Il sure hope this isn't permanent.
希望不会留下疤痕
Still no word from Star Command. We're not that far from the space port.
还是没有星计狗部的消息 我们元太空站不速了
The door. It's open! We're free!
那局门…没关好 我们自由了
- Woody, we don't know what's out there! - I'll tell you wha...
胡迪，我们不知道外面有什说 我会告诉你…
They're gonna eat us, Buzz! Do something quick!
他们要吃我们 巴斯，快想办法
Shield your eyes.
谢住眼睛
It's not working. I recharged it before I left. It should be good for...
奇怪了，我离开前才充的电 应该能发射…
You idiot! You're a toy! Use your karate chop action!
你这个白疯，你只是个玩具 用你的空手道打他们
- Get away! - Hey! Hey! How're you doin’ that?
走开 你在干什么 ?
- Stop that. - Back! Back, you savages! Back!
退后，野释人让并
- Woody, stop it! - Sorry, guys, but dinner's canceled!
胡迪，放和手 抱数，各位，不联你们玩了
There's no place like home!
我们可以回家了
Another stunt like that, cowboy, you're gonna get us killed.
你再搞这种把戏会害死我们
Don't tell me what to do.
我不用你来教我该怎广做
Yee-haw! Giddyap, pardner!
快点，伙伴
We got to get this wagon train a-movin'!
我们得让这火车拨动了
Split up!
快分散开来
Calling Buzz Lightyear. Come in, Buzz Lightyear.
呼叫巴斯光年 巴斯光年请回答
- This is Star Command. - Star Command!
这和里是星麻名部
- Buzz Lightyear, do you read me? - Buzz Lightyear responding.
星麻总部 巴斯光年，你收到吗 ?
Buzz Lightyear, planet Earth needs your help.
巴斯光年 目前地球需要你的划忙
- On the way! - Buzz Lightyear!
出动了 巴斯光年
The world's greatest superhero! Now the world's greatest toy!
全世界最棒的超级英雄 现在是全世界最棒的玩具
Buzz has it all! Locking wrist communicator!
巴斯应有画有 手腕锁定通讯器
- Calling Buzz Lightyear! - Karate chop action!
呼叫巴斯光年 还会空手道
- Wow! - Pulsating laser light!
超强雷射光束
- Total annihilation! - Multi-phase voice simulator!
微底的消减 多段式声音模拟器
There's a secret mission in uncharted space.
在一个未知的字密 有秘审任务
And best of aif, high pressure space wings!
还有最酷的高速赤翼
- To infinity and beyond! - Not a flying toy.
科向宇密浩瀚扰地
Get your Buzz Lightyear action figure
所有巴斯光年
- and save a galaxy near you! - Buzz Lightyear!
你就能拯救闭近的星床 巴斯光年
Available at aif Al's Toy Barn outlets in the tri-county area.
艾霄玩具 各大百货公司均有出售
Out among the stars I sit
月亮伴著我航行
Way beyond the moon
穿越表星星
In my silver ship I sailed
乘著银色的小船
Toadream that ended too soon
在那短暂的萝境
Now I know exactly
我现在知道自己是谁
Who I am and what I'm here for
我能说得驯
You are a toy! You can't fly!
你是玩具，你不会飞 !
And I will go sailing
我在记层和里航行
No more
哦不
But no, it can't be true
不是这样
! could fly if l wanted to
我能屎，假如我顾意
Like a bird in the sky
想像岛在天空
If l believed I could fly
自由的去飞翔
Why, I'd fly
去悉翔
To infinity and beyond!
科向宇密浩瀚扰地
Clearly, I
我
Will go sailing
不能再去…
No more
航行
Mom! Mom, have you seen my Sally doll?
杂 你有没有看到我的莎莉娃娃?
What, dear? What was that?
什么 ? 你说什么 ?
Never mind!
没事了啦
Buzz, the coast is clear. Buzz, where are you?
巴斯，安全了吐? 巴斯，你在哪里?
There's a secret mission in uncharted space. Let's go.
在一个末知的字富有秘密任务 出发
Really? That is so interesting.
是吗? 好有意思唾
Would you like some tea, Mrs. Nesbitt?
人要喝点茶吗 ? 纳斯比太太
Buzz!
巴斯
It's so nice you could join us on such late notice.
朴时邀请你 你还能来真是太好了
- Oh, no! - What a lovely hat, Mrs. Nesbitt.
烧了 好可爱的惕子，纳斯比太太
It goes quite well with your head.
你戴起来真好看
Hannah! Oh, Hannah!
汉娜
Mom? Please excuse me, ladies.
杂 失陪了，小姐们
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
What is it, Mom? Mom, where are you?
妈，什计事 ? 妈，媒哪里 ?
Buzz. Hey. Buzz, are you okay?
巴斯，巴斯，你还好吧 ?
Gone! It's all gone.
完了 全都完了
All of it's gone. Bye-bye. See ya.
全都完了，再见，和拜拜 !
What happened to you?
你是怎庆了 ?
One minute you're defending the whole galaxy.
前一分甸你还在捍本全字密
And suddenly you find yourself suckin’ down Darjeeling with
突然间 你就跟路易十六的王妃
Marie Antoinette and her little sister.
还有她的妹妹 坐在一起喝下午荣
I think you've had enough tea for today.
我想你今天 大概是茶喝得太多了
Let's get you outta here, Buzz.
快起来，跟我走吧，巴斯
Don't you get it? You see the hat?
你膛不明白吗 ? 看到得子没有 ?
- lam Mrs. Nesbitt! - Snap out of it, Buzz!
我是纲斯比太太 清醒一点，巴斯
I'm sorry. I... You're right.
你说的对
lam just a little depressed. That's all.
我只是有一黑肖囊
I can get through this.
我可以葱遇去的
Oh, I'm a sham!
我是个冒牌货
- Look at me. - Quiet, Buzz.
安静，巴斯 看看我
I can't even fly out of a window.
我甚至没有办法屎出窗外
The hat looked good? Tell me the hat looked good.
但是…这个惕子很好看 告诉我这个帽子很好看
- The apron is a bit much. - "Out the window"!
科出窗外
Buzz, you're a genius!
巴斯，你是个天才
Come on, come on. This way.
快，跟我来
Years of academy, training, wasted!
比年的辛苦训全浪费了
B-3.
B3
Miss! G-6.
没中 !66
You sunk it. Are you peeking?
你猜对了 你是不是在偷看 ?
Oh, quit your whinin' and pay up. No, no, not the ear.
不要嗓嗪了，快交出来 不…不要耳双
- Give me the nose. Come on. - How about three out of five?
把鼻子给我，快加 五战三膀怎广样
Hey, guys! Guys! Hey!
各位 !各位!
- Son of a building block. It's Woody. - He's in the psycho's bedroom.
我的老天租，是胡巡 他在那个疯子的房间壬
- Hi! - Everyone! It's Woody!
大伙鬼，是胡迪
- Woody? - You're kidding!
胡迪 真的假的?
- We're gonna get outta here, Buzz.
我们要鸠并这儿 了，巴斯
Buzz?
巴斯
- Hey, look! - Woody!
你们看 胡迪
Oh, boy, am I glad to see you guys.
老天，真高归看到你们
- [knew you'd come back, Woody. - What are you doin’ over there?
我就知道你会回来 你在那焉做什么 ?
It's a long story, Bo. I'll explain later.
说来话长，宝上中 待会儿再说
Here! Catch this!
来，接好啊
- Whoa! I've got it, Woody. - He got it, Woody.
我接到了 他接到了，胡迪
Good goin’, Slink. Now just, just tie it on to somethin’.
干得好，弹筑狗 快点找个东西绑在上面
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I got a better idea. How ‘bout we don't?
等等…我有更好的点子 列贞他的
- Hey! - Potato Head.
蛋闫
Did you all take stupid pills this morning?
你们今天是不是 都吃了策蛋药了?
Have you forgotten what he did to Buzz?
你们准道总了 他是怎广对付巴斯的?
And now you wanna let him back over here?
让他回来这好吗 ?
No! No, no, no, no, no! You got it... You got it all wrong, Potato Head.
不…你…你全都误会了 蛋闫
Buzz is fine. Buzz is right here. He's with me!
巴斯很好 巴斯在这儿四我在一起
- You are a liar! - No, I'm not. Buzz, come over here.
你是一个骗子 不，我不是，巴斯，快遇来
Tell the nice toys that you're... that you're not dead.
告诉那些好心的玩具 你…你站没有死
Buzz, will you get up here and give me a hand?
巴斯，快来助我一辟之力
That's very funny, Buzz.
你很费轩，巴斯
- This is serious! - Hey, Woody! Where'd ya go?
胡迪，你到哪儿去了?
He's lying. Buzz ain't there.
他骗人，巴斯不在那儿
Oh! Hi, Buzz!
哦，曙，巴斯?
Why don't you say hello to the guys over there?
朋友都在对面 怎广不打个招呼呢?
Hiya, fellas! To infinity and beyond!
嘛1!各位 科向宇密浩瀚扰地
Hey, look! It's Buzz!
你们看是巴斯耶
Hey, Buzz, let's show the guys our new secret best friends handshake.
巴斯，我们让好朋友们看看 我们刚刚学会的握手方式
Give me five, man!
来拍个手吧
Something's screwy here.
有点儿可疑
So you see we're friends now, guys. Aren't we, Buzz?
你们看我们现在是好朋友了 对吐，巴斯?
You bet. Give me a hug.
没错，给我个摊抱
Boy, I love you too.
老天啊，我也爱你
See? It is Buzz.
看，那是巴斯耶
- Now give back the lights, Potato Head. - Wait just a minute.
把那玩意儿给我，蛋头 你先等一下
- What are you tryin’ to pull? - Nothing!
你到底想干什么啊? 没什么
- Oh, that is disgusting. - Murderer!
真吐心耶 交手
- No! No, no, no, no, no! - You murdering dog!
不，不…- 杀人交手
- It's not what you think. I swear! - Save it for the jury.
事情不是这样，我发普 留著对陪审团说吧
l hope Sid pulls your voice box out, ya creep.
希望阿薛控出你的静音盒 淖球
No, no! No, no! Don't leave! Don't leave!
不…不要走，不要走
Ya gotta help us, please! You don't know what it's like over here!
你…你们得划攻我们 你们不知道这和里是什么科子
Come on. Let's get outta here.
好了，没什么好看的了
Go back to your lives, citizens. Show's over.
回去玩我们的吧
Come back! Slink!
回来 ! 弹筑狗
Slink! Please! Please! Listen to me!
弹簧狗，拜斌 拜斌你贩匠我说
No! No! Come back!
不，不，回来
Slinky!
弹筑狗
Buzz! Go away!
巴斯 ! 走开 !
You disgusting freaks!
你们人这些吐心的怪脸
All right, back! Back, you cannibals!
你们这些食人族快退和后 快训开 !
He is still alive, and you're not gonna get him, you monsters!
他和膛活著 你们休想吃掉他，怪物
What are you doin'?
你们在干什么 ?
Hey. Hey, they fixed you.
他们把你修好了好
But they're cannibals.
但是…他们是食人族
We saw them eat those other toys.
我们看到他们吃别的玩具
Sorry. I thought that you were gonna...
抱攻 我…我还以篇你们想…
You know, you know, eat my friend.
…吃我的朋友
Hey, no, no, wait, hey!
等等，别走 !
- What's wrong? - Sid?
怎订了 ? 阿薛
Not now, Mom! I'm busy!
等一下，妈，我有事
- Sid! Buzz, come on! - You left that door open.
巴斯，快点起来
Get up! Use your legs! Fine! Let Sid trash you! But don't blame me!
你快起来，好吧 阿薛把你给拆了，可别怪我
It came! It finally came!
害来了，终於寄来了
"The Big One."
大飞弹
"Extremely dangerous.
本物品极度危险
Keep out of reach of children."
请勿让儿童角摸
Cool! What am I gonna blow?
酷鉴了 我该炸什么呢 ?
Man. Hey, where's that wimpy cowboy doll?
那个脆小的牛仔娃娃有老
Yes. I've always wanted to put a spaceman into orbit.
好耶，我一直想把 太空人射入太空轨道
Now. Yes.
搞定了，好耶
Oh, no!
吗I不!
Oh, man!
很闫好
Sid Phillips reporting.
阿薛报告
Launch of the shuttle has been delayed
申僚发射地点天候不佳
due to adverse weather conditions at the launch site.
因此发射顺延
Tomorrow's forecast: sunny.
明天天气预报 了晴天
Sweet dreams.
祝你好欧
l looked everywhere, honey, but all I could find was your hat.
我到处都找过了 我只找到你的惕子而已
But what if we leave them behind?
如果他们被于在这里怎广办 ?
Oh, don't worry, honey.
别担心
I'm sure we'll find Woody and Buzz before we leave tomorrow.
我们明天元并以前 一定会找到胡迪和巴斯的
I need air!
我需要空气
Will you quit movin' around?
你列动来动去的
I'm sorry. It's just that I get... I get so nervous before I travel.
对不起，只是我在旅行之前 会非常的紧张
How did I get stuck with you as a moving buddy?
我怎广会选你当搬家伙伴
Everyone else was picked.
其他人都被玩光了
Oh, Woody.
哦，胡迪
If only you could see how much Andy misses you.
如果你能看到安半 他有多想你那就好了
Hey, Buzz!
嘿，巴斯
Hey. Get over here and see if you can get this toolbox off me.
快来旭我搬走这个工具箱
Oh, come on, Buzz, l...
拜斌，巴斯
Buzz, I can't do this without you. I need your help.
巴斯，没有你我办不到 我需要你的划忙
I can't help. I can't help anyone.
我帮不了你，我帮不了任何人
Why, sure you can, Buzz. You can get me outta here.
你当然可以，巴斯 你可以把我弄出去
Then I'll get that rocket off you, and we'll make a break for Andy's house.
然后我蔡你拆掉火箭 然后我们逃回安弟家去
Andy's house, Sid's house. What's the difference?
安弟家，阿薛家 有什么差别呢 ?
Oh, Buzz. You've had a big fall. You must not be thinking clearly.
巴斯，你八成摔俐了 摔得脑筋都不清楚了
No, Woody. For the first time lam thinking clearly.
不，胡迪 我的头脑第一炊这广清楚
You were right all along. I'm not a Space Ranger.
你说得对 我不是什么太空瑚警
I'm just a toy, a stupid, little, insignificant toy.
我只是一个玩具 一个愚微不足道的玩具
Whoa, hey, wait a minute.
等一下，想想看
Bein’ a toy is a lot better than bein' a, a Space Ranger.
当一个玩具 要比当什么太空戎丈好多了
- Yeah, right. - No, it is.
才怪 我说真的
Look, over in that house is a kid who thinks you are the greatest.
聘著，在那个房子里面 有个小孩认钨你是最棒的
And it's not because you're a Space Ranger, pal.
那可不是因锅你是太空骑丈
It's because you're a toy. You are his toy.
而是因锅你是玩具 你是他的玩具
But why would Andy want me?
安弟为什么会想要我呢 ?
Why would Andy want you? Look at you! You're a Buzz Lightyear.
安弟为什么会想要你 ? 看看你自己，你是巴斯光年
Any other toy would give up his moving parts just to be you.
任何玩具 都顾意被改造成像你一样
You've got wings. You glow in the dark. You talk!
你有赤翼，在黑暗中国光 还会说话
Your helmet does that, that, that whoosh thing.
你的头盔膛会… 那榜…那样打开来
You are a cool toy.
你是一个很酷的玩具
As a matter of fact, you're too cool.
老实说你真的是酷鉴了
I mean, I mean, what chance does a toy like me have
像我这种普通的玩具
against a Buzz Lightyear action figure?
怎广跟你这广有名的 巴斯光年来比呢 ?
All can do is...
我了不起只会说…
There's a snake in my boots.
我的就子里有蛇
Why would Andy ever want to play with me
安弟只要有了你就级了
when he's got you?
怎广膛会喜欢我呢?
I'm the one that should be strapped to that rocket.
我才订该被印在火稍上
Listen, Buzz, forget about me.
职好，巴斯，不要管我了
You should get outta here while you can.
趁还来得及你超快玖并吧
Buzz? What are you doin'? I thought you were...
巴斯，你在干什么 ? 我以禹…
Come on, sheriff. There's a kid over in that house who needs us.
来吧，警长 对面有个需要我们的孩子
Now let's get you out of this thing.
让我先把你弄出来
Yes, sir!
是，遵命
Come on, Buzz. We can do it.
加油，巴斯，我们办得到
Woody, it's the moving van.
胡迪，搬家货车到了
We gotta get outta here now.
我们必须快点元并
Come on, Buzz.
加油，  巴斯
All right.
好了
- Hey, I'm out! - Almost there.
巴斯，我出来了 快成功了
I want to ride the pony.
我要哺小马
Woody? Woody? Are you all right?
胡迪，胡过 你没事吧 ?
I'm fine. I'm okay.
我没事，我很好
Oh, yeah! Time for lift-off!
对了 该发射了
To infinity and beyond!
科向宇密浩瀚扰地
Back, back.
退和后…
Down, down!
走并，走开
Okay, what do I do? Come on, Woody. Think.
我该怎广办 ? 加油，胡迪，想啊，想啊
Guys!
各位
No, no, no, no! Wait! Wait. Listen, please.
不…等等 不要走，又我说
There's a good toy down there, and he's gonna be blown to bits in a few minutes.
巴斯是个好玩具 再通过分钾他就会被炸得粉碎
All because of me. We gotta save him.
都是因为我 我们必须救他
And... But I need your help.
但是我需要你们的帮忙
Please. He's my friend.
拜旗，他是我的朋友
And he's the only one I've got.
我就只剩这六一个朋友
Thank you. Okay, I think 1 know what to do.
谢谢 好了，我知道该怎麻做
We're gonna have to break a few rules.
我们要打破一些小规则
But if it works, it'll help everybody.
如果成功了 记对我们大家都好
Houston to Mission Control. Come in, Control.
体士顿呼叫管制塔 请回答
Launch pad is being constructed.
发射台已架设好了
All right, listen up.
好，台清楚了
I need Pump Boy here, Ducky here.
我要者浦到这壬 鸣子到人这儿
Legs, you're with Ducky.
长腿跟匆子一组
RollerBob and I don't move ‘til we get the signal. Clear?
我跟滑板册到讯号静才出动 伐吗 ?
Okay. Let's move!
好了，行动吧 !
Wind the frog.
替青蛙上发条
Wait for the signal.
等他的信丝
Go!
上吧
All right, let's go!
好了，我们走
I'll get it!
我来吧
Now!
街啊
I'm coming. I'm coming.
来了，来了
Scud!
阿德 !
Stupid dog.
大策狗
Lean back!
往和后仰!
Mission Control, is the launch pad construction complete?
管制塔 发射台已经完工了吐 ?
Roger. Rocket is now secured to guide wire.
收到了 火箭现在已接到半引乡
We are currently obtaining the ignition sticks.
我们现在正在装置 点火装置埋
Countdown will commence momentarily.
马上就会并始倒数计时
- Stand by. - Let's go.
待命 我们上吧
Hey, Ma! Where are the matches? Oh, wait. Here they are. Never mind.
妈，火柴在哪里? 在这壬，我找到了
Woody! Great! Help me outta this thing.
胡迪，太好了
- What? - It's okay. Everything's under control.
什么 ? 别担心，我有锦吉妙计
Woody, what are you doing?
胡迪，你在干什么 ?
Houston. All systems are go. Requesting permission to launch...
休士顿，所有系统正常
Hey? How'd you get out here?
你怎廊会在这里 ?
Oh, well. You and I can have a cookout later.
好吧，我们等一下可以烤肉
Houston, do we have permission to launch?
体士顿，我们可以发射了吗 ?
Roger. Permission granted.
收到了，请求照准
You are confirmed at "T" minus ten seconds.
倒数十秒和后就可以发射了
And counting. Ten, nine,
倒数十秒，十、九…
eight, seven, six,
八、七、六…-
five, four, three, two,
五和四、 三、二.…-
- one! - Reach for the sky!
一 把手举起来
This town ain't big enough for the two of us.
你休想在这壬和为非作碌
What?
什么啊?
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
有人对水源下了毒
- It's busted. - Who are you callin’ busted, buster?
它款掉了 是谁说我壤掉了 ?
That's right
没错
I'm talking to you, Sid Phillips.
我是在跟你说话 阿薛菲利普
We don't like bein' blown up, Sid,
我们不想被炸掉
or smashed or ripped apart.
不想被打烟 也不想被拆开
- "We"? - That's right! Your toys!
我们 ? 没错，你的玩具们
Mama!
妈妈
Mama! Mama!
妈妈…
From now on, you must take good care of your toys!
从现在起 你得好好照顾你的玩具
Because if you don't, we'll find out, Sid.
如果你不照做 我们会知道，阿薛
We toys can see everything.
我们玩具可以看到一切事情
So play nice.
所以你要乖一点
We did it! We did it! Yes!
成功了 ! 办到了 !
The toys! The toys are alive!
那些玩具…他们是活的
Nice toy.
娃娃冬竺
What's wrong, Sid?
阿薛，你是怎广了?
Don't you want to play with Sally?
你不想跟落莉玩趾?
Nice work, fellows. Good job.
干得好，各位，非常好
Comin’ out of the ground, what a touch. That was a stroke of genius.
我们合作恰快 真的是太钴采了
Woody.
胡迪
Thanks.
谢了
Everybody say, "Bye, house!”
跟羽子说再见
- Woody! The van! - Bye, house.
胡迪，你看 再见
We gotta run! Thanks, guys!
我们得走了 谢了，各位
Just go. I'll catch up.
你先走，我会超上的
Come on!
快来吧
You can do it, Woody!
胡迪，你办得到的
I got it!
我抓到了
I made it.
我成功了
Get away, you stupid dog! Down!
走并，你这焦策狗 走并，走开
- Down! - Hold on, Woody!
不要，不要 胡迪，挤著则
I can't do it.
我…我撞不住了
Take care of Andy for me!
赫我照顾安第
No!
不 !
Buzz!
巴斯
Are we there already?
已经到了吗?
- Woody? - How did you...?
胡迪 你怎广会跑来 ?
- How'd he get here? - Where have you...?
胡迪，你是怎订来的? 你到哪儿去了?
What happened?
出了什么事 ?
- What's goin' on? - What's he takin'?
他在干什么 ?
There you are!
找到了
Hey. What's he doing?
他在干什么啊 ?
He's at it again!
啊 ! 他又杀人了
- Get him! - Come on!
快去抓他
No, no!
不，不
No, no, no, no! Wait! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
不…等等…
Pig pile!
胖和猪愿顶
- Get outta that car! - Move it!
快点下车
No! Please! You don't understand!
等等，你们不明白
Buzz is out there. We gotta help him.
巴斯有和危险，我们得攻他
- No! - Toss him overboard!
不要，住手 这个条人钨手，把他丢下去
- Hooray! - So long, Woody!
好耶 胡迪，再见啦
Oh! Woody!
胡迪 !
- Oh! Well, thanks for the ride. - Look out!
谢谢你训我挫便车 小心了
Now let's catch up to that truck.
好了，我们快去追那辆卡车
Guys! Guys! Woody's riding R.C.
各位，各位 胡迪在开道控车
- What? - And Buzz is with him!
巴斯跟他在一起 什么 ?
It is Buzz!
真的是巴斯
Woody was telling the truth.
胡迪说的是实话
- What have we done? - Great! Now I have guilt.
我们做了什么啊 ? 这下好了，我有罪恶感
We're almost there!
我们就快要到了
Rocky, the ramp!
洛基，放下斜坡
Look out!
小心
Quick! Hold onto my tail!
快点，抓住我的尾巴
- Attaboy, Slink! - Oh! Woody!
干得好，弹筑狗 胡迪
Woody! Speed up!
胡迪，加速啊
- Speed up! - The batteries!
加速
Hakuna Matata
HAKUNA MATATA
What a wonderful phrase
多棒的一句话
- L can't hold on much longer. - Slink! Hang on!
我快撑不下去了 弹簧狗，你要挤住
Great!
这下好了
The match! Yes!
火柴，好了
Thank you, Sid!
谢了，阿巷
No! No, no! No!
不…-
No, no, no, no, no,
不 …-不 多
no!
不 !
- Woody! What are you doing? - Hold still, Buzz!
胡迪，你在干什么 ? 巴斯，不要动
You did it!
你办到了
Next stop: Andy!
下一站…安第
Wait a minute. I just lit a rocket. Rockets explode!
等一下，我刚刚点著了火葡 火箭会爆炸
I should have held on longer.
我应该多挤化秒的
Look! Look! It's Woody and Buzz comin’ up fast!
你们看，胡迪和巴斯生遇来了
Woody!
好耶，胡邮
Take cover!
快找掩访
This is the part where we blow up!
我们会被炸成碎片
Not today!
今天不会
Hey, Buzz! You're flyin’!
巴斯，你在赤行
This isn't flying. This is falling with style.
这不叫飞行 这叫做摔得很炫
To infinity and beyond!
科向宇密浩瀚扰地
Buzz, we missed the truck.
巴斯，我们超遇卡车了
We're not aiming for the truck.
我们站不是要到卡车上
Hey, wow!
嘿，哇塞
- What? What is it? - Woody! Buzz!
怎订了 ? 胡迪，巴斯
Oh, great, you found them. Where were they?
太好了，你找到了 它们在哪儿 ?
- Here in the car! - See?
就在车上 看吧
Now, what'd I tell you? Right where you left ‘em.
我就跟你说明你会找到的
- Which one can I open first? - Let's let Molly open one.
妈味，我先拆哪一个? 让茉莉拆一个礼物
Frankincense, this is Myrrh.
牛奶，孤到请回答
Hey, heads up, everybody. It's show time.
大伙儿，注意 好矿上场了
Oh, Bo.
宰具
There's got to be a less painful way to get my attention.
人下坎叫我 和能不能试著温柔点 ?
Merry Christmas, sheriff.
整长，桂诈快乐
Say, isn't that mistletoe?
那不是确寄生吐?
Maybe Andy will get another dinosaur. Like a leaf eater.
也许安弟会有一焦新的恐龙 草食性恐龙
That way I could play the dominant predator.
那样我就能当… 可怕的肉食动物
Quiet, everyone! Quiet!
安静，各位安才
Molly's first present is Mrs. Potato Head.
茉莉的第一件礼物是… 蛋头太太
Repeat: a Mrs. Potato Head.
重覆，蛋头太太
Way to go, Idaho!
茶喜你，蛋头见
Gee, I'd better shave.
我该刊盘子了
Come in, Frankincense.
牛奶，请回答
Andy is now opening his first present.
安弟现在正在拆 他的第一个礼物
- It's... - Buzz. Buzz Lightyear,
巴斯，巴斯光年
- 1 can't quite... - you are not worried, are you?
你不会是在担心吧?
- Me? No, no. - Make out...
我，不是… 被揽住了
No. No, no, no, no.
不 …-不 多
A large box... It's...
那是一个很大的盒子，那是…
- Are you? - Now, Buzz,
你呢 ? 巴斯
what could Andy possibly get that is worse than you?
不管安弟得到的什么礼物 都不会比你更错了
Oh, what is it? What is it?
那是什么，是什么 ?
Wow! A puppy!
哇，一焦小狗狗